qsubmit.com 2008-12-04

# Privacy Policy : Cheap Mass Search Engine Submission : Manuel Directory Submission Service : Search Engine Optimization : QSubmit.com

At QSubmit.com we know that privacy is important. The present document summarizes the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our services, and some of the measures taken to protect your information. We hope this helps you make a good decision and share your personal information with us.

This Privacy Policy is similar to the ones applied in most product services, and web sites all over the world, but QSubmit offer an added value – we are highly sensitive to the privacy concerns of our users. As part of such commitment, QSubmit.com has outlined thoroughly what information will be gathered, what security measures are in place, how your personal details will be used, and on what bases we may share it with third parties. We assure the user that we will abide by the terms of this Privacy Policy and honor your trust in our company at all times.

QSubmit.com collects personal information when you sign up, buy our services online, type in your personal details via the Contact Form, or when you contact us in any other way. However, we use a series of security procedures and technologies to protect your personal details form disclosure and/or unauthorized access.

We limit access to your information to a restricted number of company employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide you with the services that you require. When those employees leave Submir4real.com, their passwords are immediately revoked. Your confidential information, such as credit card numbers and codes, are protected by the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol’s encryption and by other security measures by our login system. 

We may use your personal information to do some statistics and improve our services, including the customization of the services you may have required. For that reason, we may use cookies and other technologies to improve your user experience online and to learn more on how you use our services, and then improve our service quality. QSubmit.com servers save the information automatically when you visit our web site or use some of our products, including your URL, IP address, language, type of browser, and the date and time of your visit. However, we DON’T SHARE THAT INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES.

We may analyze that personal information to offer you the services you have required, including services that we may create in the future. We may also use that information to check, research, and analyze how to operate and improve QSubmit’s services and technologies.

In case we hire third parties to help us process your personal information, we demand them to abide to our Privacy Policy, and we take all the necessary privacy and confidentiality measures, such as having those third parties sign an NDA

QSubmit.com may share information with third parties to prevent, investigate or take action against illegal activities, potential threat of damage to our database or servers or the the physical safety of any people, suspected fraud, violation to QSubmit.com terms of service or otherwise required by law. 

QSubmit.com processes your personal information in our servers in the USA. Thus, in some cases, we process your personal information in servers outside your country.

You may submit personal information partially and deny cookies access, but that may cause that some of our services and functions won’t operate fully.

Sumbit4real.com makes every bona fide effort to facilitate your access to your own personal information when you require it and we allow you to edit that information if incorrect in any way, and we also allow you to delete it when it is feasible. 

For more information about our Privacy Policy you may contact us via email or through the contact form on this web site at any time.
